CHI ZHANG

zchangcoding@gmail.com **Q** Edmonton **in** https://www.linkedin.com/in/chi-zhang-4a145386/ **Q** warlocksa

SUMMARY

Bootcamp time makes me master almost skills for work and get used to search solution online or ask others for help when I meet problem. Previous work experience I worked in multi-culture work environment that I was used to work with others. Customer service work also helps me learn how to find and meet what customers want. I always keep passion for new challenge that I have studied the CFA and CIFC by myself before bootcamp.

EDUCATION

| Lighthouse Lab Web Development Bootcamp | Mar. 2022 - May 2022 |
|--|------------------------|
| Mount Saint Vincent University Bachelor Tourism and Hospitality Management 2015 | Sept. 2012 - Apr. 2015 |
| Fujian Agriculture and Forest University Bachelor Agriculture Resource and Environment 2015 | Sept. 2010 - Apr. 2015 |
| EMPLOYMENT | |
| Paradies Lagardere NA, sales associate, Edmonton | Nov. 2019 - Mar. 2020 |

Holiday Inn Express & Suites Halifax - Bedford, houseperson, Halifax May 2018 - Mar. 2019 May 2014 - Dec. 2017

Fresh Happy Healthy Sushi Restaurant, cook, Halifax

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: JAVASCRIPT, RUBY, HTML, CSS, SQL:

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: NODEJS, REACT, AJAX, EXPRESS, EJS, JQUERY, RAILS:

SYSTEMS & DATABASES: POSTGRESQL, GIT: TESTING: JEST, STORYBOOK, CYPRESS:

PROJECTS

interview-scheduler Apr. 2022

React based project to create meetings for students to connect with mentors in real-time.

Tech Stack: React, Js, Axios, Storybook, Jest, Cypress.

LHL_food Apr. 2022

Pair-work project about online food order website and send the sms to both restaurant and customers.

Tech Stack: Js, Ejs, Sass, Jauery, Ajax, Sal, Api, Erd, Twilio.

Mar. 2022 tweeter

Single page project that

Feb. 2022 Tinyapp

A full stack web app built with Node and Express that allows users to shorten long URLs